divorcesource.com 2016-11-26

# Divorce Source: Privacy Statement

Divorce Source, Inc. takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy statement. 

What this Privacy Statement Covers

This Privacy Statement pertains to the treatment of personally identifiable information that Divorce Source, Inc. collects when you use certain Divorce Source Inc. services, solutions, and purchase products. 

Information Collection and Use 

Divorce Source, Inc. collects personally identifiable information when you register for our online services, solutions, and purchase products from our store environments. 

At Divorce Source, Inc., we are committed to providing our customers with the finest service, solutions, and products. And while information is fundamental to our ability to do this, we fully recognize the importance of keeping your personal and account information secure and private. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure

Divorce Source, Inc. will not sell, rent or mass distribute your personally identifiable information to anyone. 

We may share your personally identifiable information if we need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or some type of legal process; or we find that your actions on our website(s) violate our Terms and Conditions of Service, or any of our usage guidelines for specific services, solutions or products. 

Changes to this Privacy Statement

Divorce Source, Inc. may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement.
